迈凯伦加入Extreme E因为最初我们认为这是一项很不错的赛事
McLaren's entering Extreme E because first we think it's a fascinating championship.
我们在开拓创新领域有很悠久的历史
We have a long history in pioneering and innovation,
这显然也是Extreme E系列赛的基础
which is clearly what the Extreme E championship has been founded on
可持续发展和多样性，这是当今世界面临的两大问题
and sustainability and diversity, two very important issues in the world today
我们认为我们可以利用赛车这个平台展示我们的实力
and we feel we can use the racing platform to put on a great show,
同时也促进我们对可持续发展的认知
but also to accelerate our learning in sustainability
从而使这个世界变得更加美好
and being able to contribute to making the world a better place.
迈凯伦基本就是赛车运动
McLaren is basically motorsport.
迈凯伦是赛车的历史
McLaren is the history of motorsport.
迈凯伦是荣耀与光辉
McLaren is the glory.
迈凯伦在许多系列赛中都斩获过冠军
McLaren is the titles in many different championships.
同时我们也能从迈凯伦看到未来
And then also McLaren is the view of the future.
迈凯伦代表着我们希望纳入Extreme E的元素：
And McLaren represents really what we want to have in Extreme E:
一个伟大的竞争者、一支能争冠的车队
a great competitor, a team that is a winner
同时也是一支车队能和我们一样重视保护我们的地球、保护环境
but also a team that shares our values for the preservation of our planet, of the environment.
我认为这会给Extreme E增光添彩
I think it's a great addition to Extreme E.